This is
an
awesome treasure
hidden at the end of the sea,
and anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the compass points our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets, every tear that we pride
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
The long battle that divided Skypiea
for 400 years has finally ended.
Where there once was war, there
is now a joyous celebration.
No, no thanks.
I can't drink anymore.
Great!
There they are!
Hey!
What?
Go wake everyone up, quick.
But why?
Shhh!
Cause we're gonna steal the golden run.
There's gold? Where? Hey!
Quiet, loudmouth! Loudmouth, huh?
You're a whole lot louder than me, Loopy!
No way!
Just listen to yourself!
You know what you are, Nami?
Loud! What?
You're calling me loud?
You've got some nerve, you hypocrite!
You're super loud!
Oh, yeah!
Well, you're super Mock ultra loud!
That's why you're yelling!
The only reason I'm yelling is so you
can hear me over your head so loud!
What?
You two shut up!
I'm trying to sleep over here!
I didn't get it!
Stop playing with me!
I'm a lady, and ladies don't just yell
with their mouths wide open now, do that!
There's no way I do something like that!
You must have turned out here!
No, I didn't!
You have me, because it's in between!
You're looking good this morning,
but I mean, it's evening.
Boy, those blue sea people sure
do like to party, don't they?
After four days of this, you'd
think they'd be worn out.
There's no way they could be human.
So then that's the plan, guys.
I think he's right, gang.
It's not every day we get to
go to an island in the sky,
so let's make this trip worthwhile.
Chief, we found it!
We have just found the Golden Bell!
What?
Are you serious?
Yes, it's hanging off Giant Jack,
but I don't know for how long.
We're trying to pull it up right now.
We need every able-bodied
warrior at the western shore now.
We need to hurry!
Let's go! Gather the tribe!
The Belfry's been found! Where?
This way! Come on! Right!
Are you sure? Yes, hurry!
Did you hear?
They found the golden bell.
Yes. Hurry up! I'm coming.
They're on the western shore.
Move it!
They found the belfry.
Get to the western shore.
The belfry.
One more time!
One, two...
Damn it!
We still need more people!
It's the pride of Shandora.
We can't lose it.
We won't!
Give it everything you've got!
One more time!
Oh, my God!
You call this a rubber band?
Yeah, and here's a little
inside information about them.
Those babies are the primary
thing that took down Giant Jack.
Oh, my word.
And I'm the only one in
the world who has them.
Oh, wow.
But wait, there's more, namely...
This piece of metal.
Gather round, folks, and take a gander.
This is no ordinary
piece of metal, no Saru.
It came for our valiant
vessel, the Go and Merry.
It's withstood the Grand Line and
Inaru's attacks with barely a scratch.
This here's the king of metal sheets.
And just think, it can all
be yours. How about it?
Want to trade some of your dolls for this?
No, not really, but I'll gladly trade you
for this rubber band. So will I. Got more?
Me too.
I want three.
Water.
Oh, I'm so lucky!
You sure are in a good mood, Usopp.
I'm assuming your trading went well.
Oh, yeah, and Al!
Just look at all the dials I got!
One little press.
And Fall!
Well, good for you.
You mean great!
I can do so many things with them!
The old Lusop workshops are going
to be totally revolutionized!
You know what?
I could use one to store
smells in your sword!
That way you'd smell fresh-cut
melons every time you practice!
Sound good? No, thanks. Oh!
Speaking of weapons, I'm going to use
these to make Nami's climb attack stronger!
Not to mention my slingshot!
I can't wait!
So, where's everybody else, huh?
Luffy and the others are still inside.
Robin went off by herself.
Snake's still conked out, huh?
He must be really tired.
He'd be too if he danced
for four days straight.
I wonder what he was so happy about.
Anyway, I hope they come out soon.
When he wakes up, I don't
know how friendly he'll be.
Huh?
Who this well-mannered snake easy for you
to say you didn't see him when he was mad.
He's dangerous
Like I said you didn't
see him just wait till he
tries to eat you you'll
see what a pain he can be
Usopp are you even listening to me?
Fooled you with the tone dial?
Stop being so stupid!
Me stupid, but you're
the one who got fooled.
What the?
I thought Luffy ate too
much Are we there yet?
There, I told ya Wow, is it?
Yep, the real deal.
It's a bell, just like the
ones the big monkeys showed us.
See, see, see, there's so much stuff.
And it's all ours.
So that's it!
Amazing!
It's beautiful!
I didn't expect it to be so big!
It's magnificent!
Oh, but... Look!
One of the side columns
is broken off. Yeah!
What a shame! Hey!
Look over there!
Under the bell!
The poneglyph!
That thing!
So that's the stone!
Our ancestors gave their lives to protect.
Chief, the words that are
inscribed on it, what do they say?
It's an ancient text.
Impossible to read.
We shall know the true meaning
and utter it to no one.
It's our legacy to be the
inheritors of history,
and our duty to protect it with
the sounding of the Grand Belfry.
Those words, how do you know them?
They were inscribed on a wall
in the ruins of Shandora.
Generations ago, your people were
entrusted to be its guardians, correct?
You…
you can actually read
those ancient characters?
It mentions Poseidon, an ancient
weapon named after a god.
It even gives its whereabouts.
Are you certain?
Ancient weapon.
But why would it say something like that?
How odd.
Another weapon.
One different from Pluton of Alabasta.
And to think there are dangerous things
like this out there in the world,
all just waiting to be found.
Just another dead end.
This isn't what I was looking
for, what I wanted to know.
Hey miss, is that stuff engraved on
the side part of the pony glyph too?
Gold. D. Roger.
What?
I made it here,
and I will guide this passage all the
way to the farthest ends of the earth.
The stormiest seas will not
stop me, Pirate Gold Roger.
The Pirate King?
Then this could only mean that
he came to the Sky Islands.
And more importantly, how was he able to
understand and use this ancient language?
So it says Roger, does it?
You know him?
Ah, yes.
A blue sea pirate.
I met him when he came to
this land over 20 years ago.
I take it that his name
is inscribed there.
Yes.
Honestly, I have no idea how he managed
to reach this bell, but somehow he did.
And this inscription is
proof that he was here.
Wait a minute.
Now that I think about it, there
are two kinds of poneglyph stones.
Ones that contain information,
and others that tell how to reach other
poneglyphs scattered throughout the world.
This stone obviously has information.
I made it here,
and I will guide this passage all the
way to the farthest ends of the earth.
Guide this passage.
Guide
Could he Could he mean the Rio Poneglyph
Chief
This Poneglyph Its duty
has been fulfilled Its duty
Yes
I have a hunch about these Poneglyphs As I
said there were certain
ones spread across the
world that contain
information by reading them
as one i believe they'll
form a passage that
will reveal the true history of the blank
century in other words
the passage completed by
connecting them is what
will make up a legendary
final poneglyph that's
yet to be discovered
the real poneglyph gold d roger must
have taken the text from the poneglyph
here to the island where the rio
poneglyph may very well be located
he must have does that does that
mean we don't have to fight any longer
then our ancestors wish has been fulfilled
chief hang on are you all right
thank goodness our war is finally over
Well, I better get to fulfilling my duty.
Like Roger before me,
I have to guide this
passage and the other ones
I've read all the way to
the end of the Grand Line,
to the island of Raftel.
Well then, where were we?
Ah, yes.
I was about to tell you how much your
friend in the Straw Hat reminds me of Roger.
That boy is interesting.
His name's Monkey D.
Luffy, and I find him
interesting as well. D.
So the lad even shares the
same middle initial as Roger.
Yes, and I'm sure there's got to be
some historical significance to that.
Pardon me, miss,
but I recall you and your friend
saying that you sought gold,
and didn't you say it was more valuable
than Firth on the Blue Sea? Yes.
We obviously can't offer you the belfry,
but how about the broken support?
That's a great idea.
We have to give something to our heroes,
and that's a perfect
token of our appreciation.
Please take it. We insist.
Thanks, but are you sure about that?
Alright, everybody!
Let's bring this gift to our
friends from the Blue Sea!
If we wrap it up, it'll
be easier to carry!
It's gonna take every
one of us to move it!
Yeah, you're not kidding.
Oh, come on Robin.
I can't wait too long.
I'm so hungry.
There's not a soul in sight.
I've got to admit, this is pretty weird.
Wonder where all those angels
and warriors ran off to and why.
Hey, be thankful they're gone. Trust me,
if they see us making a
run for it with all the
loot we pulled from their
favorite giant snake,
Well, they're not gonna be too thrilled.
Nami and Conis probably already
have the ship ready to sell by now,
so Robin better hurry
and get back here quick.
We gotta go.
I'm hungry, Sanji.
Got anything to eat?
Nope, all the food's on the ship.
We gotta have the whole
thing to munch on, right?
Come on.
I've had enough.
I'm tired of just sitting around.
You guys can wait for her.
I'm gonna go to the ship.
Alright!
Jack!
What are you?
Stupid head!
I'll tell the guys they're all like
stupid before you have to go back here!
Hey, look! It's Robin!
Hi, hot stuff!
Hey! Robin!
Hurry up! Run!
We gotta leave!
We stole some gold! Stop it!
Look, you moron!
Right behind her, see them?
They can hear you too!
Ah! It's an army!
No, no! Not good! Not good!
That big thing can only
be one thing! A cannon.
A cannon!
Just our luck, they'd
all come back at once.
Robin!
Get the lid out!
We gotta get back to the ship now!
Check out this ghoul!
I bet we found every
piece on the island, huh?
From here, it looks like they've
already packed their bags.
Oh, no!
They're not leaving already!
Hold on you guys don't go.
Oh great. Here they come
Well, I guess it's up to
me to handle this one.
Stop. Stop.
You say like hell will stop.
We wish life and limb to come
to this island in the sky?
Capture them?
What's he talking about?
The only thing we're
trying to do is thank them!
Oh, Miss, is there a problem?
You and your friends
want this gold, right?
I guess we don't. What?
Please wait!
I can't turn around!
I know they're chasing us!
Zoro, did you see me take
care of him back there?
You're not bad.
Hey, Robin!
Better hurry up!
Hey, Robin! Wait!
Don't stop!
Until we reach Cloudy!
Bye!
When you're lost and alone?
I can always hear your voice
while you wander far from home!
Gazing up at the sky, you
are just like the moon.
You never change as you
climb into the night!
But your reflection waves when
you disappear fading so silently?
Stay as you are, don't lose your way!
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your
dreams, their endless nights!
They come to you again and again.
Until you see the journey through?
You may not turn, I hope that you learn!
To put your past behind,
and just keep moving on.